off So you the
mechanism whereby I imagined
it would happen is
that we would make
models that were good
at and good at
AI research And we
would use that to
produce the next generation
of model and speed
it up to create
a that would increase
the speed of model
development We are now
in terms of you
the models that write
code I have engineers
within Anthropa who say
don't write any code
anymore I just let
the model write the
I edit it I
do the around it
So I think I
don't know we might
be six to 12
months away from when
the is doing most
maybe all of what
do end to end
And then it's a
of how fast does
that loop close Not
every part of that
is something that can
be sped up by
AI right There's like
there's manufacture of there's
training time for the
it's you I think
there's a lot of
It's easy to see
how this could take
a years I don't
it's very hard for
me to see how
it could take longer
than that But if
I had to I
would guess that this
goes faster than people
imagine